

# Yury Kastsen

- +48881096343
- spkava@gmail.com
- Wrocław

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen</a>

Website: <a href="https://mental.gatsbyjs.io">https://mental.gatsbyjs.io</a> **Github:** <a href="https://github.com/kastsen">https://github.com/kastsen</a>

### Introduction

I see that the world can change, so I always try to link my work and hobbies with progressive projects.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

## **Experience**

12/2022 - until now

#### **Web Games Developer**

**OS** Games

Web Games Development and maintenance service:

- · CORAL ISLE 2 https://coralisle2.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · FARLAND https://farland.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · PAPAYA https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · Skills: Typescript · Webpack · Pixi JS · Create JS · React · Redux · Git · mySQL
- · REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022

#### **Playable Ads Developer**

Vizor Games

Playable ads development. Framework development and support. Build automatisation. Optimization of processes and tasks, work with the team. Skills: Node.js  $\cdot$  npm  $\cdot$  Webpack  $\cdot$  JavaScript  $\cdot$  Matter JS  $\cdot$  Bash  $\cdot$  Pixi.js  $\cdot$  Spine Animations  $\cdot$  Tiled  $\cdot$  SVN  $\cdot$  JSON  $\cdot$  ES6+

12/2019 - 03/2020

#### **Front-end Developer**

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript  $\cdot$  Node.js  $\cdot$  Express.js  $\cdot$  mySQL  $\cdot$  CSS3  $\cdot$  SCSS  $\cdot$  SPA  $\cdot$  UI  $\cdot$  Github  $\cdot$  Webpack  $\cdot$  Git  $\cdot$  SASS  $\cdot$  AJAX  $\cdot$  Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)  $\cdot$  npm  $\cdot$  ES6+  $\cdot$  API  $\cdot$  Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020 Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019 Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Work with a team, including a team of designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project. Skills: Node.js · JavaScript · CSS3 · SCSS · React · Web Design · Agile Methodologies · Scrum · UX · jQuery · Webpack · Git · SASS · AJAX · JSX · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · JSON · npm · Yarn · ES6+ · API · PHP · mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017 Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress themes and plugins.

05/2012 - 08/2014 Content management, HTML-markup

Daily News Portal

Content management, web-administrator, HTML-markup.

## **Knowledge and skills**

Languages:

Byelorussian (proficient) Russian (proficient) English (intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate)

Skills:



**Education** 

Level of education University

2015 - 2016 **Erasmus+ EVS** 

Politologie

2008 - 2012 **BSPU** 

Filologie

## **Certification and courses**

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

## **Hobbies**

Travel Yoga Music Mountains Nature